OFFICE: 
PK SOMPURA
Palitana-Bhavnagar Highway,
Near Malapara,
Palitana-364270
Mo. 9227866634/35
p k  s o m p u r a
 T e m p l e  A r c h i t e c t  &
C o n t r a c t o r  
W h e r e  D e v o t i o n  M e e t s  S t o n e .
T H R E E  G E N E R A T I O N S  O F  S A C R E D
M A S T E R Y
For more than 40 years, our family has
specialized in temple architecture. We
have completed over 51 projects
consisting of big and small temples,
combining traditional hand-carving with
modern engineering. Building on the
foundation started by our grandfather, we
remain dedicated to continuing our
family╩╝s work.
JAY MAHAKALI MAA
Under the eternal guidance of our grandfather, 
THE LATE PARSHOTTAMDAS KESHAVLALBHA SOMPURA

FERO WORKS
S T O N E  W O R K S OPERATIONAL
EXCELLENCE
We combine traditional skill with
modern technology. Our large,
advanced facility features high-
tech CNC machines, dedicated
spaces for master carvers, and
industrial cranes for safe handling
and transport.
Beyond machines, our greatest
strength is our talented team of
master carvers and assembly
experts, dedicated to ensuring
every piece fits perfectly.
CNC WORKS Fero Works: Creative structural
designs for mountain-style
temples, blending nature with
spirituality.
Stone Works: Our core legacy
hand-carved sandstone and
marble temples, built using the
ancient geometry of the Shilpa
Shastras.
CNC Works: We use advanced
computerized technology to carve
complex, sacred patterns with
mathematical precision.
SERVICES
